Guide to the Edward Scott-Snell papers M3007
Special Collections and University Archives, Colgate University Libraries
Edward Scott-Snell papers
1885-1988
M3007
Special Collections and University Archives, Colgate University Libraries
3.6 Cubic feet
Godwin, Edward
Biographical Note
After emigrating to the USA in 1948, Edward and Stephani Godwin lived in Woodstock, New York, and worked as authors and illustrators until their separation and divorce in 1955.
Books by other authors, illustrated by Edward and Stephani Godwin:
Bowie, W.R.The Bible Story for Boys and Girls: New Testament. New York: Abingdon-Cokesbury, 1951.
Bowie, W.R.The Bible Story for Boys and Girls: Old Testament. New York: Abingdon-Cokesbury, 1951.
Daringer, Helen Fern.Country Cousin. New York: Harcourt, Brace, 1951.
Daringer, Helen Fern.Debbie of the Green Gate. New York: Harcourt, Brace, 1950.
Daringer, Helen F.The Keepsake Ring. New York: Harcourt, Brace, 1953.
Deucher, Sibyl.The Young Brahms. New York: Dutton, 1949.
Eyre, Katherine Wigmore.Another Spring: the story of Lady Jane Grey. New York: Oxford University Press, 1949.
Eyre, Katherine Wigmore.The Song of a Thrush. New York: Henry Z. Walck, 1952.
Lau, Josephine Sanger.The Story of Joseph. New York: Abingdon-Cokesbury, 1950.
Meigs, Elizabeth Bleecker.The Crusade and the Cup. New York: Dutton, 1952.
Trachsel, Myrtle J.Elizabeth of the Mayflower. New York: Macmillan, 1950.
Walt Disney's Bear Country. Racine: Whitman, 1954.
Books written and illustrated by Edward and Stephani Godwin:
The Greenwood Tree: A Portrait of William Shakespeare. New York: Dutton, 1950.
Roman Eagle. New York: Oxford University Press, 1951.
Out of the Strong. New York: Oxford University Press, 1955.
The Kerlan Collection of Children's Literature at the University of Minnesota Libraries holds the manuscripts of two further novels,Brutus(accepted by O.U.P. but never published) and Dion, as well as copies of publications by other authors.
A Child's Book of Butterflies. New York: Maxton, 1956. (Edward Godwin's last published work, the text written by his second wife, Elizabeth Bridges)
Access to Collection
Collection is open for research.
Godwin, Stephani; Kelmscott Manor (Kelmscot, England).; Authors.; Correspondence.; Drawings (visual works); Illustrators.
- Letters to Edward Scott-Snell, 1929-1946
  Scope and Contents note
  About 500 letters, filed in alphabetical order, represent Edward's life during his undergraduate years at Christ Church, Oxford (attended 1930-1933) and the activities of his friends for several years afterwards. Taken as a whole, they give insight into the daily life and concerns of an undergraduate striving for success in society and in the arts. Among the interesting subdivisions are a number of letters relating to the English Club. This was a club run by undergraduates in 1931-1933 with the assistance of the poet Edmund Blunden, which invited prominent literary figures to come and speak. The President was Richard Rumbold, notorious for his undergraduate nove Little Victims, 1933, and later a biographer of Antoine de Saint-Exupery. Edward Scott-Snell was the secretary. The collection contains letters to Edward from Lord Berners; Laurence Binyon; Edmund Blunden; John Buchan; Lady Dunsany (3 letters, Lord Dunsany was a speaker at the Club); Louis Golding (2 letters); Christopher Hassall; Rose Macaulay (2 letters); John Masefield; May Morris (daughter of William Morris); Beverley Nichols; A.W. Pollard; Michael Sadler; Edith Sitwell; Osbert Sitwell (2 letters); and Una Troubridge (2 letters, she writes on behalf of Radclyffe Hall).
  Other correspondents of literary interest are the poet, Walter de la Mare (14 letters), who became quite friendly with Edward and his mother; Hector Bolitho (12 letters), a prolific historian and royal biographer; Rev. Montague Summers (4 letters), author of books on witchcraft and the occult; "Gug" Kolkhorst (4 letters), whose Sunday morning parties for aesthetic undergraduates are celebrated in John Betjeman's autobiographical poem Summoned by Bells; and Lady Lillah Keeble, formerly the Shavian actress Lillah McCarthy (4 letters), who mentionsEdward and the English Club in her memoirs,Myself and Friends.
  The collection also contains sequences of letters to Edward Scott-Snell from his closest friends. These letters are unique for their literary quality, aesthetic sensibility, affection, and the picture they give of life in the 1930s in England and abroad, especially in Italy. This series includes letters from Serge de Borchgrave (11 letters), a Belgian aristocrat and aesthete, who writes of his experiences as a draftee into the Belgian army; Archibald Colquhoun (8 letters), an artist who became a professional translator of Italian literature including works by Manzoni, Calvino, Lampedusa, etc.; Ian Greenless (13 letters), friend of the Sitwells and the homosexual-literary demimonde, later a biographer of Norman Douglas; Rodney Hindle (14 letters), a jeweller in Halifax who commissioned a bookplate from Edward; Hedley Hope-Nicholson (38 letters), an older Christ Church man, barrister, and author of the anthology,The Mind's Delight(1928) who had family connections with the Wildes and Troubridges; and Roger Venables (33 letters), Edward's closest friend, poet (especially on Cornish themes), traveller with Edward, and eloquent correspondent.
  A series of ninety-four letters to Edward Scott-Snell from his mother, Margaret Scott-Snell, provides a host of insights into the family's financial conditions, travels, and attempts to further Edward's career in Oxford and after. Although all undated, they permit an approximate reconstruction of Edward's movements, travels, and activities. There are also seventeen letters from Edward's grandfather Sir Arthur Fell (1850-1934). Fell, born in New Zealand and educated at St. John's College, oxford, was a financier and politician, standing as a Tory Member of Parliament, where he worked especially to promote building the Channel Tunnel, an idea that was shelved at the outbreak of WWI. These and the other family letters are a social document illustrating an English family's decline through the generations, from the wealthy, self-made patriarch, through his divorcee daughter Margaret, whom he supported in a small house near his Wimbledon mansion, to the gifted but financially unpromising Edward, all against a background of the 1930s, the Slump, and the shadows of war.
  - ALS from Alan to Edward Scott-Snell, no year July 9; 2 pages (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - ALS from Alan to Edward Scott-Snell, no year August 1; 4 pages (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - ALS from Alan to Edward Scott-Snell, no year September 29; 2 pages (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - TLS from Alan to to Edward Scott-Snell, no year October 4; 2 pages (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - ALS from Alan to Edward Scott-Snell, 1937 January 1; 2 pages (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - ALS from Anne to Edward Scott-Snell, no year December 2; 2 pages (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - ALS from Daniel to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 4 pages (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - ALS from Daniel to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 2 pages (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - TLS from "D" to Edward Scott-Snell, 1934 June 4; 1 page (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - ALS from Douglas to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 2 pages (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - ALS from Douglas to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 2 pages (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - ALS from Edla to Edward Scott-Snell, 1933 January 22; 4 pages (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - ALS from Elizabeth to Edward Scott-Snell, 1934 December 9; 1 page (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - ALS from Elizabeth F. to Edward Scott-Snell, 1936 February 17; 2 pages (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - ALS from Elizabeth to Edward Scott-Snell, 1937 February 17; 4 pages (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - ALS from Elizabeth to Edward Scott-Snell, no year January 25; 1 page (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - ALS from Geoffrey to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 1 page (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - ALS from Geoffrey to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 2 pages (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - ALS from Geoffrey to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 1 page (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - ALS from Geoffrey to Edward Scott-Snell, 1932 March 12; 1 page (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - ALS from Jim W. to Edward Scott-Snell, 1933 June 22; 2 pages (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - ACS from Jim W. to Edward Scott-Snell, 1933 July 8; 2 pages (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - ALS from John to Edward Scott-Snell, 1932 November 7; 2 pages (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - ALS from John to Edward Scott-Snell (beginning missing), undated; 2 pages (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - ALS from John to Edward Scott-Snell, 1932 December 21; 2 pages (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - ALS from John to Edward Scott-Snell, 1932 January 4; 2 pages (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - ALS from John W. to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 1 page (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - TLS from L. to Edward Scott-Snell, 1932 November 8; 1 page (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - ALS from Leonard H. to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 2 pages (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - ACS from Marian to Edward Scott-Snell, 1932 November 9; 1 page (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - ALS from Rachel to Edward Scott-Snell, 1935 February 26; 2 pages (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - ALS from Rachel to Edward Scott-Snell, 1936 February 21; 2 pages (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - ALS from Renee to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 4 pages (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - ALS from Renee to Edward Scott-Snell, 1935 September 16; 2 pages (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - ALS from Rheira G.to Edward Scott-Snell, 1932 February 24; 2 pages (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - ALS from William to Edward Scott-Snell, 1934 November 24; 2 pages (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - ALS from William to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 1 page (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - ALS from Stephani Allfree to Edward Scott-Snell, no year June 6; 4 pages (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - ALS from Stephani Allfree to Edward Scott-Snell, no year June 7; 3 pages (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - ALS from Stephani Allfree to Edward Scott-Snell, no year June 9; 2 pages (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - ALS from Stephani Allfree to Edward Scott-Snell, no year June 15; 5 pages (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - ALS from Stephani Allfree to Edward Scott-Snell, no year June 17; 3 pages (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - ALS from Stephani Allfree to Edward Scott-Snell, 1935 December 15; 2 pages (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - ALS from Stephani Allfree to Edward Scott-Snell, 1935 December 27; 4 pages (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - ALS from Stephani Allfree to Edward Scott-Snell, 1935 December 30; 5 pages (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - ALS from Stephani Allfree to Edward Scott-Snell, 1936 January 2; 2 pages (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - ALS from Stephani Allfree to Edward Scott-Snell, 1936 February 11; 3 pages (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - ALS from Stephani Allfree to Edward Scott-Snell, 1936 December 29; 2 pages (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - ALS from Stephani Allfree to Edward Scott-Snell, 1937 January 4; 4 pages (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - ALS from Stephani Allfree to Edward Scott-Snell, 1937 July 2; 2 pages (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - ALS from Stephani Allfree to Edward Scott-Snell, 1938 July 26; 1 page (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - ALS from Stephani Allfree to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 1 page (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - ALS from Stephani Allfree to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 2 pages (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - ALS from Stephani Allfree to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 2 pages (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - ALS from Lord B. to Edward Scott-Snell, 1932 November 2; 1 page (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - ALS from Lawrence Binyon to Edward Scott-Snell, 1932 November 7; 1 page (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - ACS from Ian D. Black to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 2 pages (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - ALS from Ian D. Black to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 2 pages (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - ALS from Ian D. Black to Edward Scott-Snell, 1933 January 20; 2 pages (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - ALS from Ian D. Black to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 4 pages (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - TLS from Basil Blackwell LH to Edward Scott-Snell, 1933 February 4; 1 page (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - TLS from Basil Blackwell to Edward Scott-Snell, 1933 February 15; 1 page (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - APS from Edmund Blunden to Edward Scott-Snell, 1933 February 18; 1 page (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - APS from Edmund Blunden to Edward Scott-Snell, 1932 November 1; 2 pages (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - ALS from Dorothy M. Boase to Edward Scott-Snell, 1937 February 17; 6 pages (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - ACS from Hector Bolitho to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 2 pages (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - ALS from Hector Bolitho to Edward Scott-Snell, no year November 18; 2 pages (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - ALS from Hector Bolitho to Edward Scott-Snell, no year February 20; 2 pages (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - TLS from Hector Bolitho to Edward Scott-Snell, no year November 29; 1 page (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - ALS from Hector Bolitho to Edward Scott-Snell, no year November 23; 2 pages (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - ALS from Hector Bolitho to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 2 pages (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - ALS from Hector Bolitho to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 1 page (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - ALS from Hector Bolitho to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 1 page (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - ACS from Hector Bolitho to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 1 page (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - TLS from Hector Bolitho to Edward Scott-Snell, 1934 February 11; 1 page (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - ACU from Serge de Borchgrave to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 1 page (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - ALS from Serge de Borchgrave to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 2 pages (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - ALS from Serge de Borchgrave to Edward Scott-Snell, 1932 December 13; 2 pages (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - ALS from Serge de Borchgrave to Edward Scott-Snell, 1933 March 29; 3 pages (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - ALS from Serge de Borchgrave to Edward Scott-Snell, 1933 June 3; 1 page (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - ALS from Serge de Borchgrave to Edward Scott-Snell, 1933 July 5; 4 pages (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - ALS from Serge de Borchgrave to Edward Scott-Snell, 1933 July 28; 1 page (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - ALS from Serge de Borchgrave to Edward Scott-Snell, 1933 August 1; 2 pages (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - ALS from Serge de Borchgrave to Edward Scott-Snell, 1933 September 24; 2 pages (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - ALS from Serge de Borchgrave to Edward Scott-Snell, 1933 October 27; 1 page (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - ACS from Serge de Borchgrave to Edward Scott-Snell, 1934 July 29; 1 page (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - ALS from Serge de Borchgrave to Edward Scott-Snell, 1934 August 4; 6 pages (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - ALS from Serge de Borchgrave to Edward Scott-Snell, 1934 October 8; 1 page (Box 1, Folder 88)
  - TLS from John Buchan to Edward Scott-Snell, 1932 November 8; 1 page (Box 1, Folder 89)
  - TLS from Hugh Chesterman to Edward Scott-Snell, 1932 October 14; 1 page (Box 2, Folder 90)
  - TLS from N. Chiereghin to Edward Scott-Snell, 1937 April 13; 2 pages (Box 2, Folder 91)
  - ALS from Archibald Colquhoun to Edward Scott-Snell, 1937 January 6; 4 pages (Box 2, Folder 92)
  - ALS from Archibald Colquhoun to Edward Scott-Snell, 1933 April 25; 4 pages (Box 2, Folder 93)
  - ACS from Archibald Colquhoun to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 2 pages (Box 2, Folder 94)
  - ALS from Archibald Colquhoun to Edward Scott-Snell, 1934 October 25; 1 page (Box 2, Folder 95)
  - ALS from Archibald Colquhoun to Edward Scott-Snell, 1935 January 1; 1 page (Box 2, Folder 96)
  - ALS from Archibald Colquhoun to Edward Scott-Snell, 1935 August 7; 2 pages (Box 2, Folder 97)
  - ALS from Archibald Colquhoun to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 4 pages (Box 2, Folder 98)
  - ALS from Archibald Colquhoun to Edward Scott-Snell, 1936 September 25; 4 pages (Box 2, Folder 99)
  - ALS from Ian W. Colvin to Edward Scott-Snell, 1931 November 5; 1 page (Box 2, Folder 100)
  - ALS from Ian W. Colvin to Edward Scott-Snell, 1932 May 31; 1 page (Box 2, Folder 101)
  - ALS from Lily S. Converse to Edward Scott-Snell, no year July 2; 2 pages (Box 2, Folder 102)
  - ALS from Helen Cooke to Edward Scott-Snell, 1933 February 14; 1 page (Box 2, Folder 103)
  - ALS from Helen Cooke to Edward Scott-Snell, 1935; 2 pages (Box 2, Folder 104)
  - ALS from Patrick Crichton-Stuart to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 4 pages (Box 2, Folder 105)
  - ALS from Patrick Crichton-Stuart to Edward Scott-Snell, no year October 25; 2 pages (Box 2, Folder 106)
  - ACS from John Crocker to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 1 page (Box 2, Folder 107)
  - T/ALS from Meurig Davies to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 2 pages (Box 2, Folder 108)
  - TLS from Walter de la Mare to Edward Scott-Snell, 1931 December 29; 1 page (Box 2, Folder 109)
  - TLS from Walter de la Mare to Edward Scott-Snell, 1931 April 27; 1 page (Box 2, Folder 110)
  - TLS from Walter de la Mare to Edward Scott-Snell, 1931 May 1; 1 page (Box 2, Folder 111)
  - TLS from Walter de la Mare to Edward Scott-Snell, 1931 August 25; 1 page (Box 2, Folder 112)
  - TLS from Walter de la Mare to Edward Scott-Snell, 1931 September 4; 1 page (Box 2, Folder 113)
  - TLS from Walter de la Mare to Edward Scott-Snell, 1931 September 8; 1 page (Box 2, Folder 114)
  - TLS from Walter de la Mare to Edward Scott-Snell, 1931 October 30; 1 page (Box 2, Folder 115)
  - TLS from Walter de la Mare to Edward Scott-Snell, 1932 April 1; 1 page (Box 2, Folder 116)
  - TLS from Walter de la Mare to Edward Scott-Snell, 1932 April 21; 1 page (Box 2, Folder 117)
  - TLS from Walter de la Mare to Edward Scott-Snell, 1932 May 12; 1 page (Box 2, Folder 118)
  - TLS from Walter de la Mare to Edward Scott-Snell, 1932 May 30; 1 page (Box 2, Folder 119)
  - TLS from Walter de la Mare to Edward Scott-Snell, 1932 October 24; 1 page (Box 2, Folder 120)
  - TLS from Walter de la Mare to Edward Scott-Snell, 1933 February 6; 1 page (Box 2, Folder 121)
  - TLS from Walter de la Mare to Edward Scott-Snell, 1946 January 7; 2 pages (Box 2, Folder 122)
  - ALS from Paul Denny to Edward Scott-Snell, 1933 March 3; 2 pages (Box 2, Folder 123)
  - ALS from Lady Dunsany to Edward Scott-Snell, 1933 January 30; 3 pages (Box 2, Folder 124)
  - ALS from Lady Dunsany to Edward Scott-Snell, 1933 May 14; 2 pages (Box 2, Folder 125)
  - ALS from Lady Dunsany to Edward Scott-Snell, 1933 May 27; 1 page (Box 2, Folder 126)
  - ALS from Elizabeth Elliot to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 1 page (Box 2, Folder 127)
  - ALS from Kate Everett to Edward Scott-Snell, 1934 May 24; 3 pages (Box 2, Folder 128)
  - ALS from Kate Everett to Edward Scott-Snell, 1934 May 21; 3 pages (Box 2, Folder 129)
  - ALS from Kate Everett to Edward Scott-Snell, 1934 May 21; 2 pages (Box 2, Folder 130)
  - ALS from Arthur Fell to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 3 pages (Box 2, Folder 131)
  - ALS from Arthur Fell to Edward Scott-Snell, 1931 January 10; 3 pages (Box 2, Folder 132)
  - ALS from Arthur Fell to Edward Scott-Snell, 1931 February 2; 2 pages (Box 2, Folder 133)
  - ALS from Arthur Fell to Edward Scott-Snell, 1931; 3 pages (Box 2, Folder 134)
  - ALS from Arthur Fell to Edward Scott-Snell, 1931 November 9; 3 pages (Box 2, Folder 135)
  - ALS from Arthur Fell to Edward Scott-Snell, 1931 November 26; 3 pages (Box 2, Folder 136)
  - ALS from Arthur Fell to Edward Scott-Snell, 1932 January 13; 3 pages (Box 2, Folder 137)
  - ALS from Arthur Fell to Edward Scott-Snell, 1932 February 14; 4 pages (Box 2, Folder 138)
  - ALS from Arthur Fell to Edward Scott-Snell, 1932 June 1; 4 pages (Box 2, Folder 139)
  - ALS from Arthur Fell to Edward Scott-Snell, 1932 October 4; 2 pages (Box 2, Folder 140)
  - ALS from Arthur Fell to Edward Scott-Snell, 1932 October 24; 2 pages (Box 2, Folder 141)
  - ALS from Arthur Fell to Edward Scott-Snell, 1932 November 11; 3 pages (Box 2, Folder 142)
  - ALS from Arthur Fell to Edward Scott-Snell, 1933 February 5; 3 pages (Box 2, Folder 143)
  - ALS from Arthur Fell to Edward Scott-Snell, 1933 March 7; 2 pages (Box 2, Folder 144)
  - ALS from John Fell to Edward Scott-Snell, no year September 1; 3 pages (Box 2, Folder 145)
  - ALS from John Fell to Edward Scott-Snell, no year June 22; 2 pages (Box 2, Folder 146)
  - ALS from John Fell to Edward Scott-Snell, no year February 9; 5 pages (Box 2, Folder 147)
  - ALS from John Fell to Edward Scott-Snell, no year February 10; 2 pages (Box 2, Folder 148)
  - ALS from John Fell to Edward Scott-Snell, no year June 16; 2 pages (Box 2, Folder 149)
  - ALS from Matilda Fell to Edward Scott-Snell, 1935 February; 3 pages (Box 2, Folder 150)
  - ALS from Phoebe Fell to Edward Scott-Snell, no year February; 1 page (Box 2, Folder 151)
  - ALS from Felix Felton to Edward Scott-Snell, 1933 April 24; 2 pages (Box 2, Folder 152)
  - TLS from Louis Golding to Edward Scott-Snell, 1932 November 21; 1 page (Box 2, Folder 153)
  - ALS from Louis Golding to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 1 page (Box 2, Folder 154)
  - ACU from Ian Greenlees to Edward Scott-Snell, 1933 September 7; 1 page (Box 2, Folder 155)
  - ALS from Ian Greenlees to Edward Scott-Snell, 1933 October 6; 9 pages (Box 2, Folder 156)
  - ALS from Ian Greenlees to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 4 pages (Box 2, Folder 157)
  - ALS from Ian Greenlees to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 2 pages (Box 2, Folder 158)
  - ALS from Ian Greenlees to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 4 pages (Box 2, Folder 159)
  - ALS from Ian Greenlees to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 14 pages (Box 2, Folder 160)
  - ALS from Ian Greenlees to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 4 pages (Box 2, Folder 161)
  - ALS from Ian Greenlees to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 6 pages (Box 2, Folder 162)
  - ALS from Ian Greenlees to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 2 pages (Box 2, Folder 163)
  - ALS from Ian Greenlees to Edward Scott-Snell, 1935 June 1; 4 pages (Box 2, Folder 164)
  - ALS from Ian Greenlees to Edward Scott-Snell, no year December 25; 3 pages (Box 2, Folder 165)
  - ALS from Ian Greenlees to Edward Scott-Snell, 1936 December 28; 2 pages (Box 2, Folder 166)
  - ALS from Ian Greenlees to Edward Scott-Snell, 1937 July 19; 2 pages (Box 2, Folder 167)
  - ALS from Christopher Hassall to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 1 page (Box 3, Folder 168)
  - ALS from Christopher Hassall to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 1 page (Box 3, Folder 169)
  - ALS from John A. Hayward to Edward Scott-Snell, 1932 October 23; 2 pages (Box 3, Folder 170)
  - ALS from Viola Head to Edward Scott-Snell, no year June 26; 2 pages (Box 3, Folder 171)
  - ALS from Viola Head to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 2 pages (Box 3, Folder 172)
  - ALS from Rodney Hindle to Edward Scott-Snell, 1931 November 2; 1 page (Box 3, Folder 173)
  - ALS from Rodney Hindle to Edward Scott-Snell, 1931 December 12; 4 pages (Box 3, Folder 174)
  - ALS from Rodney Hindle to Edward Scott-Snell, 1932 January 22; 4 pages (Box 3, Folder 175)
  - ALS from Rodney Hindle to Edward Scott-Snell, 1932 January 27; 1 page (Box 3, Folder 176)
  - ALS from Rodney Hindle to Edward Scott-Snell, 1932 March 1; 2 pages (Box 3, Folder 177)
  - ALS from Rodney Hindle to Edward Scott-Snell, 1932 April 13; 2 pages (Box 3, Folder 178)
  - ALS from Rodney Hindle to Edward Scott-Snell, 1932 May 17; 2 pages (Box 3, Folder 179)
  - ALS from Rodney Hindle to Edward Scott-Snell, 1932 May 29; 8 pages (Box 3, Folder 180)
  - ALS from Rodney Hindle to Edward Scott-Snell, 1932 October 23; 4 pages (Box 3, Folder 181)
  - ALS from Rodney Hindle to Edward Scott-Snell, 1932 November 29; 5 pages (Box 3, Folder 182)
  - ALS from Rodney Hindle to Edward Scott-Snell, 1933 January 23; 6 pages (Box 3, Folder 183)
  - ALS from Rodney Hindle to Edward Scott-Snell, 1933 May 7; 5 pages (Box 3, Folder 184)
  - ALS from Rodney Hindle to Edward Scott-Snell, 1933 May 22; 3 pages (Box 3, Folder 185)
  - ALS from Rodney Hindle to Edward Scott-Snell, 1933 May 30; 2 pages (Box 3, Folder 186)
  - ALS from Rodney Hindle to Edward Scott-Snell, 1933 August 8; 5 pages (Box 3, Folder 187)
  - ALS from Rodney Hindle to Edward Scott-Snell, 1933 November 1; 7 pages (Box 3, Folder 188)
  - ALS from Rodney Hindle to Edward Scott-Snell, 1934 July 12; 6 pages (Box 3, Folder 189)
  - ALS from Charles Holmes to Edward Scott-Snell, 1929 November 27; 2 pages (Box 3, Folder 190)
  - ALS from Charles Holmes to Edward Scott-Snell, 1932 May 26; 2 pages (Box 3, Folder 191)